{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_3_BQKBRT",
                "player_6_BQKBRT"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                3,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    2243.944,
                    870.979,
                    246.691,
                    0,
                    30.17373851609966,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    1878.81,
                    343.178,
                    479.008,
                    0.0,
                    -89.999,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_BQKBRT"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    2569.625,
                    994.67,
                    335.882,
                    0,
                    86.98578304720917,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            1497.07,
            903.804,
            359.521
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1299.384036768772
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            1792.966,
            32.157,
            446.938,
            0,
            58.12899723612149,
            0
        ],
        [
            1338.003,
            997.148,
            278.669,
            0,
            -16.288917504396906,
            0
        ],
        [
            2239.124,
            981.849,
            234.946,
            0,
            -91.95334942707689,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "B. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many distinct entities are present in this vast, frozen expanse, including both human figures and aerial devices?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Amidst the desolate landscape, how many aerial vehicles are depicted?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many of the human figures moving across the desolate landscape possess light skin?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Disregarding any non-human elements, how many figures are present who are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. waving"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the White Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Below"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the White Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}